<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>tamiltoddlers</title>
    <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io" />
    <updated>2021-05-18T14:50:20+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>SrideviG</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Disclaimer</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/disclaimer.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/disclaimer.html</id>

        <updated>2021-05-16T21:15:11+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    GENERAL INFORMATION Tamiltoddlers (“company”, “I”, “we” or “us”) provides general educational information on various topics on this website as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>GENERAL INFORMATION</strong></p>
<p>Tamiltoddlers (“company”, “I”, “we” or “us”) provides general educational information on various topics on this website as a public service, which should not be construed as professional or educational advice. These are my personal opinions only.</p>
<p>The term “you” refers to anyone who uses, visits and/or views the website.</p>
<p>Please read this Disclaimer carefully, and I reserve the right to modify it at any time without notice.  <strong>By visiting and using this website, you accept and agree to be bound by this Disclaimer along with our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our website, programs, products and/or services constitutes your acceptance of future changes and updates to this Disclaimer. You must not access or use our website if you do not wish to be bound by this Disclaimer.</strong></p>
<p><strong>GENERAL DISCLAIMER</strong></p>
<p>All content and information on this website including our programs, products and/or services is for informational and educational purposes only, does not constitute any kind of professional advice and does not establish any kind of professional-client relationship by your use of this website. An professional-client relationship with you is only formed after we have expressly entered into a written agreement with you that you have signed including our fee structure and other terms to represent you in a specific matter. Although we strive to provide accurate general information, the information presented here is not a substitute for any kind of professional advice, and you should not rely solely on this information. Always consult a professional in the area for your particular needs and circumstances prior to making any professional, legal, educational and financial or tax related decisions.</p>
<p><strong>AFFILIATE / THIRD-PARTY LINKS DISCLOSURE AND DISCLAIMER</strong></p>
<p>We may partner with other businesses or become part of different affiliate marketing programs whose products or services may be promoted or advertised on the website in exchange for commissions and/or financial rewards when you click and/or purchase those products or services through our affiliate links. We will receive a commission if you make a purchase through our affiliate link at no extra cost to you.</p>
<p>We may also recommend other products, services, coaches and consultants but no such reference is intended to be an endorsement or statement that such information provided is accurate. We recommend these based on our personal experiences but it is still your responsibility to conduct your own due diligence to ensure you have obtained complete accurate information about such product, services, coaches and consultants.</p>
<p>We are a participant in the Amazon Influencer program, which is an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.in</p>
<p>These affiliate or third party relationships in no way compromise the integrity of the content, information, services and materials being presented to you here, and you are under no obligation to click on these affiliate links to purchase those products or services being offered. These affiliate programs are selected based on personal experiences and preferences.</p>
<p>Although we provide these affiliate links on the website for your convenience, we have no control over these external websites and they are solely responsible for their own content and information presented.  Therefore,Tamiltoddlers and/or its officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us cannot be held liable or responsible for any content presented on these external websites and for any damages resulting from them.</p>
<p>This disclosure policy applies to all affiliate links we share on our website, social media, emails, programs, products such as courses, ebooks, services and any other means of communication with you.</p>
<p><strong>EARNINGS DISCLAIMER, TESTIMONIALS AND OTHER DISCLAIMERS</strong></p>
<p>We may disclose our income reports and success results of our current or former customers including product reviews and testimonials on the website from time to time. These income reports, product reviews and testimonials are accurate and strictly for informational purposes only.</p>
<p>We share this information as <u>examples</u> to you but it does not serve as a guarantee or promise of any kind for your results and successes if you decide to use the same information, reviews, products, services, tips and techniques offered here.</p>
<p>All the testimonials included on our websites, programs, products and/or services are real-world examples and stories of other people’s experiences with our programs, products and/or services. But they are not intended to serve as a guarantee that you will achieve the same or similar results. Each individual’s performance is different and your results will vary accordingly.</p>
<p>You are encouraged to perform your own due diligence and research and are solely responsible for your earnings and results. Your earning potential and results are contingent upon your personal circumstances, abilities, experience, and skills. Therefore, you agree not to hold us and/or our officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us liable for any of your successes or failures directly or indirectly related to the information, reports, reviews, products and/or services presented to you here.</p>
<p><strong>SPONSORED POSTS / REVIEWS DISCLAIMER</strong></p>
<p><strong> </strong>We may include sponsored blog posts on our website from time to time for products or services we recommend or those that have been valuable in our personal experience or use.</p>
<p>We may review different products, services, and other resources to provide reviews of books, services and any other recommendations to you. We may receive incentives, discounts, compensation or free products in exchange for our reviews and sponsored content. All such reviews and sponsored posts are solely our honest opinions made in good faith. You are always encouraged to perform your own due diligence prior to relying on them.</p>
<p>We share this information as <u>examples</u> to you but it does not serve as a guarantee or promise of any kind for your results and successes if you decide to use the same information, reviews, products, services, tips and techniques offered here.</p>
<p>You are encouraged to perform your own due diligence and research and are solely responsible for your decisions, purchases from our affiliate links, sponsored content and results. Your earning potential and results are contingent upon your personal circumstances, abilities, experience, and skills. Therefore, you agree not to hold us and/or our officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us liable for any of your successes or failures directly or indirectly related to the information, reports, reviews, products and/or services presented to you here.</p>
<p><strong>FAIR USE DISCLAIMER </strong></p>
<p>This website reviews products, services including but not limited to posting of product images from other websites, logos of manufacturers. If you believe any material has been used in an unauthorized manner, please contact us at tamiltoddlers@gmail.com</p>
<p><strong>NO WARRANTIES</strong></p>
<p>ALL CONTENT, INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES ON THE WEBSITE ARE “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR ANY PURPOSE, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY LAW. COMPANY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE CONTENT, INFORMATION, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES PROVIDED ON THIS WEBSITE. COMPANY MAKES NO WARRANTIES THAT THE WEBSITE WILL PERFORM OR OPERATE TO MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR THAT THE INFORMATION PRESENTED HERE WILL BE COMPLETE, CURRENT OR ERROR-FREE. COMPANY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, IMPLIED AND EXPRESS FOR ANY PURPOSE TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.</p>
<p><strong>LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</strong></p>
<p>You agree that under no circumstances, we and/or our officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us shall be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, equitable, special, punitive, exemplary or any other damages resulting from your use of this website including but not limited to all the content, information, products, services and graphics presented here.</p>
<p>You expressly agree that your use of the website is at your sole risk and that you are solely responsible for the accuracy of the personal and any information you provide, outcome of your actions, personal and business results, and for all other use in connection with the website.</p>
<p>You also expressly agree that we and/or our officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us shall not be liable to you for any damages resulting from 1) any errors or omissions on the website, delay or denial of any products or services, failure of performance of any kind, interruption in the operation and your use of the website, website attacks including computer virus, hacking of information, and any other system failures; 2) any loss of income, use, data, revenue, profits, business or any goodwill related to the website; 3) any theft or unauthorized access by third party of your information from the website regardless of our negligence; and 4) any use or misuse of the information, products and/or services offered here.</p>
<p>This limitation of liability shall apply whether such liability arises from negligence, breach of contract, tort or any other legal theory of liability. You agree that we provide no express or implied guarantees to you for the content presented here, and you accept that no particular results are being promised to you here.</p>
<p><strong>INDEMNIFICATION</strong></p>
<p>You agree to indemnify and hold the Company and/or its officers, employees, successors, shareholders, joint venture partners or anyone else working with us harmless from all losses, claims, damages, demands, actions, suits, proceedings or judgments, including costs, expenses and reasonable attorneys’ fees (“Liabilities”) assessed against or otherwise incurred by you arising, in whole or in part, from: (a) actions or omissions, whether done negligently or otherwise, by you, your agents, directors, officers, employees or representatives; (b) all your actions and use of our websites including purchasing programs, products and services; (c) violation of any laws, rules, regulations or ordinances by you; or (d) violation of any terms and conditions of this website by you or anyone related to you; e) infringement by you or any other user of your account of any intellectual property or other rights of anyone. The company will notify you promptly of any such claims or liability and reserves the right to defend such claim, liability or damage at your expense. You shall fully cooperate and provide assistance to us if requested, without any cost, to defend any such claims.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cancellation Policy </title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/cancellation-policy.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/cancellation-policy.html</id>

        <updated>2021-05-16T20:57:35+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Shipping Policy We offer shipping to overseas on request. Cancellation of Orders Cancellation can only be affected if the order has&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div id="comp-jdwwh5l1" class="_2bafp" >
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f5qsfksu0" class="font_2">Shipping Policy</h2>
</div>
<div id="comp-kh01i55l" class="_10k60">   </div>
<div class="_10k60">We offer shipping to overseas on request. </div>
<div id="comp-kh01ay5d" class="_2bafp" >
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f5qsfksu1" class="font_2">Cancellation of Orders</h2>
</div>
<div id="comp-kh13deqw" class="_10k60"> </div>
<div id="comp-kh01bj1b" class="_2bafp" >
<p class="font_8">Cancellation can only be affected if the order has not been dispatched. To cancel, please send an email quoting the reference number, with the subject ‘Cancellation’, to tamiltoddlers@gmail.com</p>
</div>
<div id="comp-kh13by0b" class="_2bafp" >
<h2 id="mcetoc_1f5qsfksu2" class="font_2">Replacement and Refund</h2>
</div>
<div id="comp-kh01ir9d" class="_10k60"> </div>
<div id="comp-kh13etiv" class="_2bafp" >
<p class="font_8">All sales are final except in cases of defective product or if there has been an error on our part. In case if you suspect that the package has been tampered with or damaged, you may reject it at the time of the delivery. The request for replacement of damaged books must reach us within 24 hours of delivery, along with the video of the defective or damaged product. If accepted, either another copy of the same product will be sent to you or the amount will be refunded. Refund will be done online in 7 - 14 working days.</p>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>FAQ</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/faq.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/faq.html</id>

        <updated>2021-05-16T20:53:09+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    1. What does the Tamil Flashcard set include? Tamil Flashcards set includes Uyir ezhuthukkal, Mei ezhuthukkal and Uyirmei ezhuthukkal&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>1. What does the Tamil Flashcard set include? </p>
<p>Tamil Flashcards set includes Uyir ezhuthukkal, Mei ezhuthukkal and Uyirmei ezhuthukkal ( a total of 52 cards).</p>
<p>2. How many days will you take to ship the Flashcards? </p>
<p>The shipping time includes 7-14 days</p>
<p>3. How to get refund for damaged product? </p>
<p>We will require the cusotmers to take a video while opening the product and share it with us. If the damage happens on shipping Tamiltoddlers are not responsible for the same except under exceptional circumstance. However video is mandatory.</p>
<p>4. Do you give refund for digital bundle? </p>
<p>No refund is given for digital bundle. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Digital Worksheets</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/digital-woeksheets.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/digital-woeksheets.html</id>

        <updated>2021-05-16T20:16:10+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Give your little ones a headstart to Tamil language with our amazing set of worksheets. We feel these worksheets&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Give your little ones a headstart to Tamil language with our amazing set of worksheets. We feel these worksheets will you in your journey of introducing the world's oldest language "Tamil" to your little ones.</p>
<p>Please click on the image (you will be redirected to our Instamojo store).</p>
<p class="align-left"><a href="https://tamiltoddlers.stores.instamojo.com/product/407611/uyir-ezhuthukkal-worksheets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Uyir ezhuthukkal bundle"><img class="post__image--left" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/38/instamojo-pic.png" alt="Uyir ezhuthukkal bundle 1" width="720" height="1040"></a></p>
<p>  <a href="https://tamiltoddlers.stores.instamojo.com/product/351080/ula-varum-uyir-ezhuthukkal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Ula varum Uyir ezhuthukkal"><img class="post__image--left" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/38/instamojo.png" alt="Ula varum uyir ezhuthukkal" width="1040" height="720"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://tamiltoddlers.stores.instamojo.com/product/398754/merukootum-mei-ezhuthukkal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Mei ezhuthukkal bundle"><img class="post__image--left" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/38/Slide1.PNG" width="720" height="1040"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>How can you use this? </p>
<p>You can use these in n number of ways! One method I can share for using it repeatedly is to laminate them.</p>
<ol>
<li>Download these worksheets.</li>
<li>Print them</li>
<li>Laminate them (for repeated usage)</li>
<li>Buy velcro (use for cutting and pasting activities)</li>
</ol>
<p> Kindly note these are <strong>digital bundle and NO physical products will be shipped.</strong></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Letter of the week எ</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-series.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-series.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-16T15:11:54+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/37/1-5.png" alt="" />
                    Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil : Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/37/1-5.png" alt="" />
                <p>Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil :</p>
<ul>
<li>Loads of free printables</li>
<li>Hands on activity ideas</li>
<li>YouTube videos and explanations of works<br><br><br><img class="post__image" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/37/1-5.png" alt="" width="1080" height="1080"></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p>Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel <a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Tamiltoddlers">www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers</a> for  fun activities.</p>
<p>For daily dose of fun activities ,follow us on Instagram:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Insta Link">www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers</a></p>
<p>For now, here are some of the printables for the next Tamil letter எ , you can download them for FREE.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> <a href="../../../../../media/files/7poster.pdf" title="Poster">Poster </a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/7match.pdf">Matching எ</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/7numbercount.pdf">Tamil numbers and counting</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>TAMIL FLASHCARD SET</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/tamil-flashcard-set.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/tamil-flashcard-set.html</id>

        <updated>2021-05-12T13:03:06+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.35-PM.jpeg" alt="" />
                    Thank you for your overwhelming response!! We are OUT OF STOCK ( update as on May 10,2021 ). However&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.35-PM.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">Thank you for your overwhelming response!!</p>
<p>We are <strong>OUT OF STOCK ( update as on May 10,2021 ). </strong>However we have launched few Tamil worksheet bundles (DIGITAL). Download from anywhere , Print (Laminate), Use and Learn :))</p>
<p><strong>Tamil worksheets: <a href="tamiltoddlers.stores.instamojo.com">Tamil digital bundle</a></strong></p>
<p>This Flashcard set contains a total of 52 cards which includes</p>
<ul>
<li>Uyir ezhuthukkal</li>
<li>Mei ezhuthukkal </li>
<li>UyirMei ezhuthukkal (First series)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>SHIPPING ONLY ON THURSDAYS. </strong></p>
<p>Printed in 300 GSM matte paper.</p>
<p>Card size: 9 * 13 cms</p>
<p> </p>
<p>WE ALSO DO <strong>INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING on REQUEST! </strong></p>
<p>You can write to <a href="mailto:tamiltoddlers@gmail.com">tamiltoddlers@gmail.com</a> if you're looking to buy Tamil Flashcards outside India. :) </p>
<p>We have served to customers from Singapore and Norway ! </p>
<p>To purchase our Flashcards , please pay through below link:</p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.33-PM.jpeg" ><img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.33-PM-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="768" height="1024"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.36-PM.jpeg" ><img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.36-PM-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="768" height="1024"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.37-PM-1.jpeg" ><img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/36/gallery/WhatsApp-Image-2021-01-01-at-9.51.37-PM-1-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="768" height="1024"></a></figure>
</div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<a href="https://www.instamojo.com/@tamiltoddlers/l15d005e130d74d46940bf4c5e8a470d3/" rel="im-checkout"    ></a>
<script src="https://js.instamojo.com/v1/button.js"></script>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Letter of the Week ஊ</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-uu.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-uu.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-16T15:13:30+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/35/1-3.png" alt="" />
                    Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil : Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/35/1-3.png" alt="" />
                <p>Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil :</p>
<ul>
<li>Loads of free printables</li>
<li>Hands on activity ideas</li>
<li>YouTube videos and explanations of works<br><br><br><img class="post__image" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/35/1-3.png" alt="" width="1080" height="1080"></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p>Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel <a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Tamiltoddlers">www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers</a> for  fun activities.</p>
<p>For daily dose of fun activities ,follow us on Instagram:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Insta Link">www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers</a></p>
<p>For now, here are some of the printables for the next Tamil letter உ , you can download them for FREE.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/6poster.pdf" title="Poster ஊ">Poster ஊ</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/6match.pdf" title="Matching concept ஊ">Matching concept ஊ</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/6reptiles.pdf" title="Reptiles ஊர்வன">Reptiles ஊர்வன</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Letter of the week- உ</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-u.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-u.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-16T15:14:54+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/34/a-3.png" alt="" />
                    Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil : Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/34/a-3.png" alt="" />
                <p>Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil :</p>
<ul>
<li>Loads of free printables</li>
<li>Hands on activity ideas</li>
<li>YouTube videos and explanations of works<br><br><br><img class="post__image" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/34/5.png" alt="" width="1080" height="1080"></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p>Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel <a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Tamiltoddlers">www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers</a> for  fun activities.</p>
<p>For daily dose of fun activities ,follow us on Instagram:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Insta Link">www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers</a></p>
<p>For now, here are some of the printables for the next Tamil letter உ , you can download them for FREE.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> <a href="../../../../../media/files/5 poster.pdf" title="உ Poster">உ Poster</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/5 piggybank.pdf" title="Piggy bank">Piggy bank</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/5 match.pdf" title="Match the letters">Match the letters</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Letter of the week - ஈ</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-ii.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/letter-of-the-week-ii.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-16T15:15:03+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/33/a-6.png" alt="" />
                    Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil : Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/33/a-6.png" alt="" />
                <p>Here’s what you can expect Letter of the Week Tamil :</p>
<ul>
<li>Loads of free printables</li>
<li>Hands on activity ideas</li>
<li>YouTube videos and explanations of works<br><br><br><img class="post__image" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/33/1.png" alt="" width="1080" height="1080"></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p>Make sure you have subscribed to my YouTube channel <a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Tamiltoddlers">www.youtube.com/c/Tamiltoddlers</a> for  fun activities.</p>
<p>For daily dose of fun activities ,follow us on Instagram:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Insta Link">www.instagram.com/tamiltoddlers</a></p>
<p>For now, here are some of the printables for the next Tamil letter ஈ , you can download them for FREE.</p>
<p> <img class="post__image" src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/33/a-6.png" alt="" width="940" height="788"></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/dot marker.pdf">Dot Marker ஈ</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/Emu.pdf">Emu bird</a></p>
<p><a href="../../../../../media/files/Matching.pdf">Matching Printable ஈ</a></p>
<p> </p>
<div class="”sharethis-inline-share-buttons”"> </div>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Uyir Ezhuthukkal bundle</title>
        <author>
            <name>SrideviG</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/uyir-ezhuthukkal-bundle.html"/>
        <id>https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/uyir-ezhuthukkal-bundle.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-01T22:52:55+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/32/Colour-the-Uyir-eluthu.png" alt="" />
                    Happy to launch our worksheet bundle on "Uyir ezhuthukkal". Check out this video to know the content of the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://tamiltoddlers.github.io/media/posts/32/Colour-the-Uyir-eluthu.png" alt="" />
                <p>Happy to launch our worksheet bundle on "Uyir ezhuthukkal".</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Check out this video to know the content of the bundle: </p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/ehQtvGzm1mo">Uyir Ezhuthukkal Bundle DIGITAL</a></p>
<p>Click the below link to make the payment now! (THIS IS A TEST LINK, PLEASE CHECK WITH <a href="mailto:tamiltoddlers@gmail.com">tamiltoddlers@gmail.com</a> for PAYMENT! )</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
